<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Agile Development on Experiments, Thoughts and Reflection</title>
    <link>https://kaushalbundel.com/categories/agile-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Agile Development on Experiments, Thoughts and Reflection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kaushalbundel.com/categories/agile-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Client/end User&#39;s Discovery process</title>
      <link>https://kaushalbundel.com/posts/2021-01-26-client-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaushalbundel.com/posts/2021-01-26-client-discovery/</guid>
      <description>Pre Client Discovery process
Get a small write up from the concerned stakeholder defining what is needed/expected out of the call Check the preposition offered What&amp;rsquo;s being offered to the client? What are some pros and cons of the offering? Whats the expected outcome and output? What are some of the competitors? What&amp;rsquo;s the usp of the solution implemented by major competitors? Confirm if the client has done some sort of similar task earlier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on UAT</title>
      <link>https://kaushalbundel.com/posts/2021-01-20-uat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaushalbundel.com/posts/2021-01-20-uat/</guid>
      <description>What is UAT?
UAT is User Acceptance testing. Essentially it is a testing performed by the end user/client before moving the software application to the production environment.
What&amp;rsquo;s the need of UAT?
capture the requirement in a direct and verifiable manner identify problems which unit/integration tests might have missed tells how &amp;ldquo;done&amp;rdquo; the system is Steps to do an effective UAT
Plan the UAT Preparation of the test data, scenarios and test environment UAT test scheduling and management UAT testing execution and issue management Testing signoff and reporting Types of UAT</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
